http://www.kwikool.com/privacy-policy/

Share
EmailTwitterFacebookGoogle +PinterestTumblrLinkedinVkontakte
KwiKool
Portable Commercial Cooling Systems
Privacy Policy
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, or fill out a form.
When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: Name, email address, mailing address or phone number. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
To personalize your experience (Your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs.)
To improve our website (We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.)
To improve customer service (Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.)
To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)
To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature
To send periodic emails (The email address you provide for order processing may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.)
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from KwiKool Portable Cooling Systems emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database, only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems. Those individuals are required to keep the information confidential.
Do we use cookies?
We do not use cookies.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies or protect ours or others rights, property or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act.) We do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy only
This online Privacy Policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your consent
By using our site, you consent to the Privacy Policy.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.This policy was last modified on 07/01/2018
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, you may contact us using the information below.
KwiKool Portable Cooling Systems
10404 Mula Rd
Stafford, Texas 77477
USA
Contact:
sales@kwikool.com
